Unit 7, recording 38.
Now to begin with, there are two main variables called G-Under score Move and G-Under score Turn.
The first one, G-Under score Move, tells the robot which way to go, back, forward or stay still.
If G-Under score Move is zero, the robot doesn't move.
Okay.
The second variable, G-Under score Turn, tells it to turn left, turn right or not to turn.
I see. So if G-Under score Turn is zero, it doesn't turn.
That's right.
Now, look at the first line of the code here.
It sets G-Under score Move and G-Under score Turn to zero.
Telling it not to move and not to turn.
That's right.
I see. And the next line?
See this variable here? Key underscore Press.
This has the value of the key pressed on the phone.
So, if you press A on the phone, for example, key underscore Press has the value A.
And...
If I press the X key on the phone, key underscore Press takes the value X.
Yep. You've got it.