Unit 7, recording 39.
Now, let's look at the IF statements.
See the four of them here?
Yep.
Now, the first one looks at key underscore press.
IF key underscore press is A,
then G underscore move becomes one.
In other words, pressing A on the mobile phone
means that G underscore move takes the value of one.
That's correct.
And later in the program, we'll see that if G underscore move is one,
the robot moves forwards a step.
I see.
So, looking at the next line,
if you press F on the phone,
G underscore move becomes two,
and the robot moves forwards two steps.
Well, the first bit's right, yes.
G underscore move becomes two,
but two actually makes the robot move back a step.
Hmm.
I see.
So, for the next one,
if you press S,
I can see that G underscore turn becomes one.
But does that make the robot turn right or left?
It turns left.
So pressing D makes it turn right.
That's correct.