Унижается 7, в речи 40.
Okay, let's have a quick look at the Gantt chart.
What's our schedule?
Well, the systems analysts are finishing their tasks at the end of week 3.
So your team is scheduled to start coding in week 4.
Then the second milestone, being ready for alpha testing, is due in week 9.
So we have five weeks to do the coding.
Yep, that's right.
And then the alpha testing is due to finish at the end of week 10.
So your schedule to deal with the feedback from that in week 11.
And we have two weeks to do that.
And then according to the chart, we start again in week 16 after the alpha testing.
Hmm, we only have a week after the beta testing.
That doesn't sound very long.
You're right, that's rather short.
I think there's a mistake.
The beta testing should only last two weeks, not three.
So you should have two weeks to deal with the feedback.
I'll change the chart.
Two weeks for beta testing.
And two weeks after that, for you to do the debugging.
Okay, that's better.
Thanks very much.
No, that's okay.
We should still be able to finish the project before week 18.